**Privacy Policy / Terms of Use**

(Amended as of Feb. 5, 2020)

This Online Privacy Policy applies to www.fhamortgageplace.com, owned and operated by FHA Mortgage Place (sometimes referred to as “FHA Mortgage Place”), and any Company affiliate or subsidiary online interface that links to this Policy, (each, a “Site,” and collectively, the “Sites”). This Policy describes how FHA Mortgage Place collects and uses the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information.

This Web site is not directed at persons under the age of 18. By using this Site you consent to this Online Privacy Policy, including your consent to our use and disclosure of information about you in the manner described herein. When you register with this website, you explicitly authorize us to share your information.

If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy, please do not complete the information request form (i.e., do not register) or otherwise use or access this Site. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at [https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

Our Privacy Policy explains what information we obtain on this Site, and how we use the information disclosed to us to link you to our business affiliates who have expressed a willingness to provide you with the products and services associated with this Site.

**Who We Are**

We are an on-line consumer service that introduces persons such as yourself to certain of our business affiliates who have expressed a general willingness to review your information and determine if they are willing to provide you with the services or products that prompted you to visit our Site. When you visit our Site, you will be requested to complete provide certain information that our business affiliates request in order to perform a preliminary analysis of your qualifications to receive the service or products. Based upon your consent, as evidenced by your registering with us on this Site (i.e., your submission of the requested information on the application), we will forward the information that you provided to certain of our business affiliates.

In addition, from time to time, we or our business affiliates may provide you the additional service (the "Premium Service") of sending you e-mail you or otherwise corresponding with you to inform you of additional opportunities to receive special offers for other services and/or products that we believe may be of interest. There are no fees for Premium Service, and you are under no obligation to accept any service or product with any of our business affiliates offered under the Premium Service.

**Information We Collect**

We collect the information that you submit and which our business affiliates consider necessary for performing a preliminary evaluation of your qualifications for their products and services.

We may collect the following personal information from you:

* name; address; e-mail address; telephone number; fax number; credit card information; information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services; education level; educational interests; home owner status; income; debt level; current mortgage; mortgage rate and the like.

**Information Use**

WE MAY USE INFORMATION THAT WE HAVE COLLECTED FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE, INCLUDING SELLING OR TRANSFERING SUCH INFORMATION AT ANY TIME TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE.

We use your information to:

* Send you requested product or service information
    
* Provide you with you requested information
    
* Respond to customer service requests
    
* Send you a newsletter
    
* Send you marketing communications
    
* Provide information to our affiliates
    
* Respond to your questions and concerns
    
* Optimize and enhance your experience on our Site; as well as provide you with an efficient, safe, smooth, and customized experience

**Sharing Information**

As noted throughout, we send, sell and transfer information to our business associates for the purpose of providing you with requested services. We may share your personal information with select business affiliates so that they can contact you and offer you products and or services that we believe might be of interest to you. This may include e-mail advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, and online banner advertising to name a few. In addition, we may maintain separate e-mail, mailing or phone lists for different purposes based on the information that you submitted and that we maintain. For your information, our business affiliates have all agreed to operate in accordance with federal and state laws and regulations relating to the handling of your personal information. You may learn more about any of our business affiliate's privacy policy by visiting our business affiliates' Web sites at such times as such affiliate may contact you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of our business affiliates' Web sites. If you wish to end any e-mail correspondence from us, you will need to Opt-out from receiving further correspondence by advising us of your decision to Opt-out by clicking a link in the e-mail to our Opt-out procedures. Within ten (10) business days, your e-mail address will be placed on a suppression list and we will no longer correspond with you by email or resell or transfer your information to third parties. If you wish to end future correspondence with any of our business affiliates, you will need to follow the instructions at the end of any such each e-mail message from them to unsubscribe from such business affiliate's e-mail. You are able to opt-out when registering with us.

We may also disclose your personally identifiable information in response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process; as well as the transfer or sale of personally identifiable information pursuant to the sale of our business or assets. Should such a combination or acquisition occur, we will require that the new combined or acquiring entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If we transfer ownership of the site to another company, we will notify you by email or by general notice on our site. In addition to the forgoing, we may also sell, transfer or share non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons visiting this site.

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, third parties may unlawfully intercept personal data or access our servers and obtain personal data. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, nor you should not expect, that your personal information would always remain private.

Certain sensitive information such as credit card numbers or other information such as social security numbers and drivers licenses ("Financial Information") collected on the site and associated data is encrypted and protected with SSL encryption software from the time it is captured by our application to the time it is transmitted to our servers. For more information on the encryption and protection of your information, please see How We Protect Your Privacy.

**Premium Services and Information Validation**

Prior to sending your information to our business affiliates, we attempt to validate it. For example, we may compare and review your personal information for errors, omissions, and accuracy based upon past usage and response; or compare your information against other publicly available files; or validate some of the personal information submitted to verify that the information inputted has a high probability of being valid information.

After we submit your information to our business affiliates, our business affiliates may begin a separate and independent evaluation of the information you submitted (the "Preliminary Application"). If our business affiliates find that the Preliminary Application meets with their more specific acceptance criterion, they may contact you directly by phone, mail or e-mail. For more information on how our business affiliates will handle your personal information, please visit our business affiliate's website, and review their privacy policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of our business affiliates' Web sites.

Once you have registered with us, you are automatically enrolled to receive our Premium Service. We use the information you provided, along with other information described below, to create a general user profile. This profile can be created by combining your information with other sources of information such as information obtained from public databases, or from your browsing habits surrounding your visit to this Site. We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including wireless services that display customized content and advertising. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. If you remove your SMS information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you.

**Legitimate Interests**

We use cookies, log files, enhanced email, connected mobile, and connected TV communications for our legitimate interests of providing you with relevant and personalized interactions

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

_Cookies_

A cookie is a digital file that contains a string of text, storing information. Commonly, web servers which host and maintain websites send cookies to your computer. They are usually stored on your computer via your web browser. The web browser communicates information related to your interactions with the website, back to the web server of the website. This is a common way to drive personalization across internet enabled devices, as the storing of this information allows the website to know what it should know about you based on what you previously looked at or interacted with.

We use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

_Log Files_

A log file is a digital file that records interactions between software systems. Log files exists across all internet and IP enabled devices, including the connected mobile, connected TV, and enhanced email tactics described herein. Device type and location using latitude and longitude coordinates can also be stored.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or page views.

We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We may record your IP addresses when you place an order through our site in order to detect and prevent fraud.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by [clicking on this link](https://www.fhamortgageplace.com/opt-out.php). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

The Do Not Track browser settings

Advertisers may collect data about your online browsing activity and use it to show you targeted ads (a process known as "behavioral advertising").

You can prevent companies from showing you targeted ads by submitting opt-outs to those service providers.

Opting-out will only prevent targeted ads so you may continue to see generic (non-targeted ads) from these companies after you opt-out.

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If you wish to request access, or deletion of your personal information please contact us at unusubscribcfmp@seememail.net

We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

**Application of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have signed up on the website. We may sell the personal information that you supply to us and we may work with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via direct mail, email and telemarketing. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing

How We Protect Your Privacy

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can mail us at the address indicated below in the Contact Us section.

**Opting-Out**

If you want to request to be removed from further communication with this Site, including our Premium Services, please Opt-out by [clicking on this link](https://www.fhamortgageplace.com/opt-out.php) to our Opt-out procedure. We will place your e-mail address on a suppression file associated with this Site. Persons whose names appear on our suppression file, will have their e-mail addresses checked against all correspondence to be sent by us. Where there is a match, the planned email correspondence will be withheld, and such person will receive no further email correspondence from us. Your e-mail address will be placed on the suppression list associated with this Site within ten business (10) days of your request. Once you have opted out, we will no longer forward you email from this site but we are not responsible or in control of the business practices of our business affiliates who have been forwarded your information.

**Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy on the Site. Be sure to check the current terms of any privacy policy in effect by visiting this Site. By checking the effective date of the policy, you will be immediately alerted on whether the Privacy Policy has been updated. Please note however, that the updated privacy policy will go into effect automatically 30 days after initial posting. From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. Please note that if our information practices change at some time in the future, we will use only data collected from the time of the new privacy policy amendment forward for those new purposes. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.  

**Special Notification for California Residents**

If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights concerning our collection and use of your personal information. After reading this Online Privacy Policy, please click [here](https://www.fhamortgageplace.com/privacypolicyca.php) to visit FHA Mortgage Place’s California Privacy Notice to learn more about your California Privacy Rights.

DISCLOSURES

When inquiring about a loan on this site, this is not a loan application. This is not an offer to lend and we are not affiliated with your current mortgage servicer. Upon the completion of your inquiry, we will work hard to match you with a lender or lenders who may assist you with an official loan application and provide loan product eligibility requirements for your individual situation.

When applying for a loan, lenders will commonly require you to provide a valid social security number and submit to a credit check. Consumers who do not have the minimum acceptable credit required by the lender are unlikely to be approved. Minimum credit ratings may vary according to lender and loan product. In the event that you do not qualify for a credit rating based on the required minimum credit rating, a lender may or may not introduce you to a credit counseling service or credit improvement company who may or may not be able to assist you with improving your credit for a fee. Any loan product that a lender may offer you will carry fees or costs including closing costs, origination points, and/or refinancing fees. In many instances, fees or costs can amount to several thousand dollars and can be due upon the origination of the loan product.

This site is in no way affiliated with any news source or government organization and is not a government agency. Not affiliated with HUD, FHA, VA, FNMA or GNMA. This site may contain affiliate and partner links. This website and the company that owns it is not responsible for any typographical or photographic errors. If you do not agree to our terms and policies, then please leave this site immediately. If you submit your mobile number on this website you agree to receive marketing based text messages. Consent is not required for purchase. You will receive up to 4 messages per month. Standard text and data rates may apply. Reply STOP to stop & HELP for help.

Contents of this website are copyrighted property of the owner of this website. All trademarks, logos, and service marks (collectively the "Trademarks") displayed are registered and/or unregistered Trademarks of their respective owners.

In the event that you discovered this website through an advertisement, such advertisement may consist of stock photos, images, video or other publicly available resources. Any spokesperson used is an employee of the advertiser that owns and operates this website and is not a paid spokesperson or influencer.

© 2024 FHA Mortgage Place is not a government agency or a lender. Not affiliated with HUD, FHA, VA, FNMA or GNMA. We work hard to match you with local lenders for the mortgage you inquire about. This is not an offer to lend and we are not affiliated with your current mortgage servicer.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
  
ATTN: FHA Mortgage Place  
1550 W Horizon Ridge Pkwy R Suite #R 610  
Henderson, NV 89012  

**Please print and retain a copy of this privacy policy for your records.**
